chocolate.com 2009-04-03

# Privacy Policy

Shop By Season

  * Easter Gifts,
  * Mother's Day Gifts

Shop By Price

  * Gifts On Sale,
  * Gifts Under $25,
  * Gifts Under $50,
  * Gifts Under $75,
  * Gifts Under $100

Shop By Occasion

  * Birthday Gifts,
  * Wedding Gifts,
  * New Baby Gifts,
  * Get Well Gifts,
  * Wedding Favors

Shop By Gift Type

  * Corporate Gifts,
  *  Gift Boxes,
  * Chocolate Gift Baskets,
  * Chocolate Gifts

Shop By Category

  * Chocolate Truffles,
  * Milk Chocolate,
  * Dark Chocolate,
  * White Chocolate,
  * Gourmet Chocolate,
  * Brownies,
  * Cakes,
  * Cookies,
  * Fudge,
  * Chocolate Candy,
  * Chocolate Bars,
  * Popcorn,
  * Baking Chocolate

Shop By Ingredients

  * Sugar Free Chocolate,
  * Kosher Chocolates ,
  * Organic Chocolates,
  * Fair Trade Chocolate
  * Chocolate Covered Fruits,

Latest Products

SpringChoc \- This solid chocolate egg delivers an incredibly subtle kiss of refreshing essential oils and energizing, rich cacao. Let a spring breeze of Jasmine, Lemon Grass, and Lavender whisk away all your winter worries! This solid ...

Wine Chocolates From The Santa Cruz Mountains \- SPECIAL! Our assortment of wine chocolates includes chocolates that we make for some of the finest wineries in the Santa Cruz Mountains Appellation in Callifornia. They include 2003 Merlot from Burrell School, 1997 Blanc de Blanc ...

Mothers Are Forever Large Gift Basket \- Mothers ARE forever! Show Mom how much you care with this incredibly beautiful gift basket adorned in roses, all designed in honor of Mom. Available in Small, Medium, and Large (pictured) sizes. Mothers ARE forever! Show Mom ...

Heart Healthy Gourmet With Salmon Gift Basket \- A gift specially designed for that health-conscience person in your life - nothing bland here! Spoil someone special with these flavorful snacks and gourmet treats that are delicious and GOOD FOR YOU! (** Please note food items ...

Pink Be Happy Sugar Cookie Bags \- Super cute cookies that are guaranteed to bring a smile to your face. Each ribboned cookie sleeve contains eight (8) 2.5" round vanilla iced sugar cookies. Priced just right! A Dozen Eggs cookies are hand made in Vermont. We specialize ...

Latest Articles

**Chocolate.com Privacy Statement**   
By visiting Chocolate.com, you are accepting the practices described in this Privacy Statement. 

**What Personal Information About Customers Does Chocolate.com Gather?**   
For your long-term privacy and security of your credit card, we do not save credit card numbers after orders are complete.

We use other information that you provide for such purposes as responding to your requests, customizing future website enhancements for you, improving our products, and communicating with you. 

**Automatic Information**  
Like many other web sites, we use "cookies," and we obtain certain types of information when your Web browser accesses www.chocolate.com such as the referring page and your IP address 

**E-mail Communications**   
To help us improve the quality of our email content, we may receive a confirmation when you open e-mail from Chocolate.com if your computer supports such capabilities. 

Emails sent for promotional purposes are sent ONLY to those users who opt-in to receive them. Every email for this purpose also contains a link to change your email preferences, and/or opt-out. 

**Does Chocolate.com Share the Information It Receives?**  
Information about our customers is an important part of our business, and we do not sell it to others. We share customer information only as described below. 

**Agents**  
We employ other companies and individuals to perform functions on our behalf. Examples include fulfilling orders, delivering packages, sending postal mail and e-mail, providing marketing assistance, processing credit card payments, and providing customer service. They have access to personal information needed to perform their functions, but may not use it for other purposes. 

**Business Transfers**  
As we continue to develop our business, we may be acquired by or purchase other businesses. In such transactions, customer information generally is one of the transferred business assets but remains subject to the promises made in any pre-existing Privacy Notice (unless the customer consents otherwise). 

**Protection of Chocolate.com and Others**  
We release account and other personal information when we believe release is appropriate to comply with the law; enforce or apply our Conditions of Use and other agreements; or protect the rights, property, or safety of Chocolate.com users, or others. This includes exchanging information with other companies and organizations for fraud protection and credit risk reduction. We will not under any condition sell, rent, share, or otherwise disclose personally identifiable information from customers for commercial purposes in violation of the commitments set forth in this Privacy Notice. 

**No Disclosure Without Your Consent**  
If an unforseen condition ever arises where Chocolate.com wishes to disclose your information to a third party, you will have an opportunity to choose not to share the information. 

**How Secure Is Information About Me?**  
We work to protect the security of your information during transmission by using Secure Sockets Layer (SSL) software, which encrypts information you input. We reveal only the last four digits of your credit card numbers when confirming an order. Of course, we transmit the entire credit card number to the payment gateway and credit card company during order processing. 

It is important for you to protect against unauthorized access to your password and to your computer. Be sure to sign off when finished using a shared computer. 

**Which Information Can I Access?**   
Chocolate.com gives you access to information about your account and your interactions with Chocolate.com for the limited purpose of updating that information. 

**What Choices Do I Have?**  
As discussed, you can always choose not to provide information, even though it might be needed to make a purchase or to take advantage of Chocolate.com features. 

**Children**  
Chocolate.com does not sell products directly to children. If you are under 18, you may purchase products from Chocolate.com only with the involvement of a parent or guardian. 

**Conditions of Use, Notices, and Revisions**   
If you choose to visit www.chocolate.com, your visit and any dispute over privacy is subject to this Notice and our Conditions of Use, including limitations on damages, arbitration of disputes, and application of the law of the state of Massachusetts. 

Our business does change, and our Privacy Notice and the Conditions of Use may also change. We may e-mail periodic reminders of our notices and conditions, unless you have instructed us not to, but you may want to check our web site to see recent changes. Unless stated otherwise, our current Privacy Notice applies to all information that we have about you and your account. 

We stand behind the promises we make, however, and will never materially change our policies and practices to make them less protective of customer information collected in the past without the consent of affected customers. 

_Next Article:_   Contact Us

All Chocolate Articles | Christmas Chocolate | Corporate Gifts
